Nick Valkov

Gameplay Programmer

Work Experience





Avalanche Studios Group

Lead Senior Gameplay Programmer August 2023 to Present.

Senior Gameplay Programmer March 2023 to July 2023 (5 months).



Arrowhead Game Studios

Lead Gameplay Programmer March 2021 to February 2023 (2 years).

Gameplay Programmer
December 2019 to February 2021 (1 year, 3 months).

Education History

Bachelor of Game Design and Programming Institution: Uppsala University - Campus Gotland Period: 2016 to 2019

 Studied Game Design with Programming as a minor. Created 3 separate small games as group projects as part of the education.

Side Projects

Freelancher - Worked as a freelance programmer for about 7 years, making various mods for people.

Modding - Have spent around 10 years modding games such as Garry's Mod, Payday 2 and XCOM 2.

Summary

A gameplay programmer by title and a modder at heart.

Whether it's in the industry or as an amateur, I've been working with games for well over 10 years now.

Contact Info



Portfolio / Website



LinkedIn



Email

Relevant Skills

- Strong knowledge of: C++, C, Lua, C#
- Proficiency in English (8.5/9 IELTS) and Bulgarian (Native).
- Team management and planning